{
 "subject": "biology",
 "lesson": "l01",
 "grade": "c4",
 "quests": [
	{
		"id": 1,
		"question": "Microorganisms are measured in _______.",
		"options": {
			"a": "cm",
			"b": "mm",
			"c": "micron",
			"d": "meter"
		},
		"answer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": 2,
		"question": "______ shows both living and nonlivingcharacteristics.",
		"options": {
			"a": "Protozoa",
			"b": "Virus",
			"c": "Bacteria",
			"d": "Fungi"
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 3,
		"question": "______ is a prokaryotic microorganisms.",
		"options": {
			"a": "Virus",
			"b": "Algae",
			"c": "Fungi",
			"d": "Bacteria"
		},
		"answer": "d"
	},
	{
		"id": 4,
		"question": "Based on shape, the bacteria are classified into _______ types.",
		"options": {
			"a": "two",
			"b": "three",
			"c": "four",
			"d": "five"
		},
		"answer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": 5,
		"question": "Common cold in human is caused by_____.",
		"options": {
			"a": "plasmodium",
			"b": "influenza",
			"c": "vibrio cholera",
			"d": "aphthovirus"
		},
		"answer": b"
	},
	{
		"id": 6,
		"question": "Disease causing microorganisms arecalled pathogens.",
		"options": {
			"a": "true
			"b": "false",",
			"c": "",
			"d": ""
		},
		"answer": "a"
	},
	,
	{
		"id": 7,
		"question": "Female anopheles mosquito is a carrier of
dengue virus.",
		"options": {
			"a": "true
			"b": "false",",
			"c": "",
			"d": ""
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id":8,
		"question": "Chicken pox is a communicable disease.",
		"options": {
			"a": "true
			"b": "false",",
			"c": "",
			"d": ""
		},
		"answer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 9,
		"question": "Citrus canker is transmitted by insects.",
		"options": {
			"a": "true
			"b": "false",",
			"c": "",
			"d": ""
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 10,
		"question": "Yeast is used in the large scale productionof alcohol.",
		"options": {
			"a": "true
			"b": "false",",
			"c": "",
			"d": ""
		},
		"answer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 11,
		"question": "Nitrogen fixing bacteria ",
		"options": {
			"a": "Vaccine",
			"b": "Prion",
			"c": "Rhizobium",
			"d": "Bacteria"
		},
		"answer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": 12,
		"question": "Tuberculosis",
		"options": {
			"a": "Vaccine",
			"b": "Prion",
			"c": "Rhizobium",
			"d": "Bacteria"
		},
		"answer": "d"
	},
	{
		"id": 13,
		"question": "Probiotics",
		"options": {
			"a": "Lactobacillus",
			"b": "Prion",
			"c": "Rhizobium",
			"d": "Bacteria"
		},
		"answer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 14,
		"question": "Kuru",
		"options": {
			"a": "Vaccine",
			"b": "Prion",
			"c": "Rhizobium",
			"d": "Bacteria"
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 15,
		"question": "Edward Jenner",
		"options": {
			"a": "Vaccine",
			"b": "Prion",
			"c": "Rhizobium",
			"d": "Bacteria"
		},
		"answer": "a"
	}
  ]
}